<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tracker Water</string>
    <string name="inights">Inights</string>
    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="today">Today</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="drink">Drink</string>
    <string name="hydrated_text">
        Drink <font color="#0247C8">200-300ml of water</font> each time to stay well-hydrated
    </string>
    <string name="records">Records</string>

    <string name="choose_your_age">Choose your age</string>
    <string name="age_text2">The daily water intake needs of people of different ages vary</string>

    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>

    <string name="how_weigh">How much do you weigh?</string>
    <string name="exercise_text">How much exercise do you do each week</string>
    <string name="RarelyExercise">Rarely exercise</string>
    <string name="SometimesExercise">Sometimes exercise</string>
    <string name="RegularlyExercise">Regularly Exercise</string>
    <string name="OftenExercise">Often exercise</string>
    <string name="Hot">Hot</string>
    <string name="Temperate">temperate</string>
    <string name="cold">Cold</string>
    <string name="wake_up">When do you usually wake up?</string>

    <string name="meal">What\'s your usual meal time?</string>
    <string name="dont_eat_lunch">I don\'t eat lunch</string>
    <string name="dont_eat_breakfast">I don\'t eat breakfast</string>
    <string name="dont_eat_dinner">I don\'t eat dinner</string>
    <string name="wakeup_drink">Drinking water 1 hour before sleep will keep you hydrated during your sweet dream</string>
    <string name="synData">Synchronize Data ></string>
    <string name="total_dirk">Total Drinking</string>
    <string name="reminder">Reminders</string>
    <string name="total_achieved">Total Achieved</string>
    <string name="version">Version 1.3.3 A</string>
    <string name="daily_goal">Daily Goal</string>
    <string name="sound_vibration"><![CDATA[Sounds & Vibration]]></string>
    <string name="units">Units</string>
    <string name="genders_weight"><![CDATA[Gender & Weight]]></string>
    <string name="language_options">Language Options</string>
    <string name="english">English</string>
    <string name="first_dayOweek">First Day Of Week</string>
    <string name="Day_StartAt">A Day Starts At</string>
    <string name="time_format">Time Format</string>
    <string name="RemoveAds">Remove ads</string>
    <string name="feed_back">Feedback</string>
    <string name="rate_us">Rate Us</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="day">day</string>
    <string name="week">Week</string>
    <string name="goal">Goal</string>
    <string name="total">Total</string>
    <string name="oz">Oz</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="Day_StartAt0">A day starts at 00:00</string>
    <string name="aday_start_at2">Records before 00:00 willbe included in the count for the previous day.</string>
    <string name="water_drop1">Water drop 1</string>
    <string name="water_drop2">Water drop 2</string>
    <string name="water_flowing1">Water flowing 1</string>
    <string name="water_flowing2">Water flowing 2</string>
    <string name="water_flowing3">Water flowing 3</string>
    <string name="sound_effect">Sound effect</string>
    <string name="vibration">Vibration</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="month">Month</string>
    <string name="we_just_need_to_ask_a_few">We just need to ask a few questions to customize your daily goal and schedule.</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_your_smart_water_tracker">Welcome to your smart water tracker</string>
    <string name="drink_water_live_better">Drink water, live better.</string>
    <string name="your_gender_helps_us_suggest">Your gender helps us suggest a more accurate daily water intake goal.</string>
    <string name="what_s_your_gender">What’s your gender?</string>
    <string name="other">Other</string>
    <string name="i_m_pregnant">I’m pregnant</string>
    <string name="i_m_breastfeeding">I’m breastfeeding</string>
    <string name="male">Male</string>
    <string name="female">Female</string>
    <string name="people_of_different_ages_have">People of different ages have varying daily water intake needs.</string>
    <string name="daily_water_intake_varies_significantly_by_weight">Daily water intake varies significantly by weight.</string>
    <string name="daily_water_intake_varies_with_exercise_levels">Daily water intake varies with exercise levels.</string>
    <string name="the_hotter_the_climate_the_higher_your_daily_water_intake_should_be">The hotter the climate, the higher your daily water intake should be.</string>
    <string name="hydrating_right_after_waking_up_boosts_your_energy_in_the_morning">Hydrating right after waking up boosts your energy in the morning!</string>
    <string name="we_ll_remind_you_to_drink_an_hour_before_and_after_meals_for_optimal_digestion_and_weight_loss">We’ll remind you to drink an hour before and after meals for optimal digestion and weight loss</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="defaults">Defaults</string>
    <string name="hours">hours</string>
    <string name="minutes">min</string>
    <string name="seconds">seconds</string>
    <string name="ml">ml</string>
    <string name="l">L</string>
    <string name="us_oz">US Oz</string>
    <string name="uk_oz">UK Oz</string>
    <string name="your_daily_goal_is">Your daily goal is</string>
    <string name="adjust">Adjust</string>
    <string name="excludes_35_of_water_from_food">Excludes 35% of water from food.</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="avoid_these_water_drinking_mistakes">Avoid these water drinking mistakes</string>
    <string name="insights">INSIGHTS</string>
    <string name="water_drinking_title_1">Common Mistakes to Avoid When Drinking Water\n</string>
    <string name="water_drinking">Water Drinking</string>
    <string name="water_drinking_title_2">Best Times to Drink Water</string>
    <string name="water_drinking_title_3">Replacing Sugary Beverages with Water for Better Healt</string>
    <string name="water_drinking_title_4">Drink Water on an Empty Stomach?</string>
    <string name="water_drinking_title_5">Benefits of Drinking Lemon Water</string>
    <string name="water_drinking_title_6">Is It OK to Drink Water During a Meal?</string>
    <string name="water_drinking_title_7">Drink Water: The Benefits for Health</string>
    <string name="water_drinking_title_8">Dangers of Overhydration</string>
    <string name="water_drinking_title_9">Why You Shouldn\'t Give Babies Water</string>
    <string name="beauty_skincare_title_1">Drinking Schedule for Wrinkle-Free Skin</string>
    <string name="beauty_skincare_title_2">Juices for Radiant and Glowing Skin</string>
    <string name="beauty_skincare_title_3">Hot and Cold Water Benefits for Skin</string>
    <string name="beauty_skincare_title_4">Promote Hair Growth with Water</string>
    <string name="beauty_skincare"><![CDATA[Beauty & Skincare]]></string>
    <string name="self_care_title_1">Effective Fat-Burning Beverages for Weight Loss</string>
    <string name="self_care_title_2">What to Drink During Fasting</string>
    <string name="self_care_title_3">Top Fat-Burning Drinks for Weight Loss</string>
    <string name="self_care_title_4">What to Drink During Fasting</string>
    <string name="self_care_title_5">Drink Water to Lose Weight: How to Do It</string>
    <string name="self_care_title_6">Benefits of Hydration for Exercise</string>
    <string name="self_care">Self-care</string>
    <string name="health_life_style_title_1">Effective Fat-Burning Beverages for Weight Loss</string>
    <string name="health_life_style_title_2">What to Drink During Fasting</string>
    <string name="health_life_style_title_3">Drink Water to Lose Weight: How to Do It</string>
    <string name="health_life_style_title_4">Benefits of Hydration for Exercise</string>
    <string name="health_life_style_title_5">Soothe Sore Throats with These Drinks</string>
    <string name="health_life_style_title_6">Drinks to Relieve Stomach Bloating</string>
    <string name="health_life_style">Health Lifestyle</string>
    <string name="unit_ml">ml</string>
    <string name="recent">Recent</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="you_should_drink_100_3000ml_at_once">* You should drink 100–3000ml at once.</string>
    <string name="average">Average</string>
    <string name="noti_title">Notification title</string>
    <string name="noti_content">Notification content</string>
    <string name="reminder_title">Reminder title</string>
    <string name="reminder_content">Reminder content</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item1_Opening_des">Did you know that how you drink water can influence your health?\n\nLet’s uncover the most frequent water-drinking mistakes and simple ways to stay properly hydrated and healthy.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item1_Screen_1_title">The Consequences of Not Drinking Enough Water</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item1_Screen_1_des">Not drinking enough water can lead to health problems like headaches, low energy, and digestive issues such as constipation.\n\nSince hydration needs vary for each person, you can use our app to determine your ideal daily water intake and get timely reminders to maintain optimal hydration.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item1_Screen_2_title">Drinking Too Much Water</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item1_Screen_2_des">Overhydration can cause hyponatremia, a condition where excess water dilutes the sodium levels in your body. This can be especially dangerous for athletes and individuals with heart or kidney conditions.\n\nSymptoms of hyponatremia include nausea, headaches, confusion, seizures, and, in severe cases, even coma.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item1_Screen_3_title">Not Drinking Clean Water</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item1_Screen_3_des">Ensuring the water you drink is clean and free of harmful contaminants is essential for your health. If you\'re uncertain about the safety of your tap water, consider using a reliable water filter or opting for bottled water from trusted sources.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item1_Screen_4_title">Drinking Water Too Quickly</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item1_Screen_4_des">Drinking water too quickly can cause bloating, discomfort, and nausea. It also reduces your body’s ability to absorb the water efficiently, often leading to frequent restroom trips.\n\nTo stay hydrated without these issues, sip water slowly and steadily throughout the day.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item1_Screen_5_title">Drinking Cold Water</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item1_Screen_5_des">Cold water can cause blood vessels to constrict, potentially slowing digestion and reducing blood flow to your organs. For some individuals, drinking very cold water may also trigger headaches or migraines.\n\nTo avoid these effects, consider drinking water at room temperature or slightly chilled.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item1_Screen_6_title">Skipping Water Before Bed</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item1_Screen_6_des">Even while you sleep, your body continues important functions like tissue repair and toxin removal. Not drinking enough water before bed can lead to dehydration, causing headaches, dry mouth, and even disrupting your sleep quality.\n\nA small amount of water before bed can help keep your body hydrated throughout the night.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item2_Opening_des">We all understand the importance of drinking enough water, but did you know that when you drink can be just as crucial as how much you drink?\n\nHere are some of the best times to hydrate throughout the day for optimal health and well-being.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item2_Screen_1_title">After Waking Up</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item2_Screen_1_des">Drinking water first thing in the morning helps kickstart your metabolism, rehydrate your body after hours of sleep, and flush out toxins.\n\nStart your day with a glass of water before consuming any food or other beverages to maximize these benefits.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item2_Screen_2_title">Before Meals</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item2_Screen_2_des">Drinking water before meals can help you feel fuller, reduce the likelihood of overeating, and support digestion by preparing your stomach for food.\n\nFor best results, aim to drink water about 30 minutes before each meal.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item2_Screen_3_title">After Meals</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item2_Screen_3_des">Drinking water after meals can help with digestion and prevent constipation. However, it\'s important to wait at least 30 minutes after eating before drinking water to allow your stomach to properly digest the food.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item2_Screen_4_title">Before and During Exercise</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item2_Screen_4_des">Staying hydrated before and during exercise helps prevent dehydration, which can cause fatigue and muscle cramps.\n\nAim to drink water 2–3 hours before your workout and take small sips every 10–20 minutes during exercise to maintain optimal hydration.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item2_Screen_5_title">Before Bed</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item2_Screen_5_des">Drinking water before bed supports overall hydration but should be done in moderation to avoid frequent trips to the bathroom at night. Aim for a small glass of water about an hour before bedtime to stay hydrated without disrupting your sleep.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item3_Opening_des">It’s time to ditch sugary drinks and make water your go-to choice.\n\nDiscover the 7 key benefits of choosing water over sugary beverages below.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item3_Screen_1_title">Weight Loss</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item3_Screen_1_des">Water contains zero calories, making it a great choice for those looking to reduce calorie intake. By replacing sugary or high-calorie beverages like soda and sweetened drinks with water, you can significantly lower your calorie consumption, helping to create a calorie deficit essential for weight loss and preventing unwanted weight gain.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item3_Screen_2_title">Improved Digestion and Nutrient Absorption</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item3_Screen_2_des">Water helps keep the lining of the digestive tract healthy and promotes regular bowel movements, preventing constipation. Additionally, drinking water with meals can aid digestion by diluting stomach acids, making it easier for your body to break down and absorb nutrients from food.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item3_Screen_3_title">Better Skin Health</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item3_Screen_3_des">Dehydration can lead to dry, flaky skin and exacerbate conditions like acne and eczema. By replacing sugary drinks with water, you help flush out toxins from your body and maintain your skin\'s elasticity and suppleness, promoting a healthier complexion.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item3_Screen_4_title">Enhanced Brain Function</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item3_Screen_4_des">Dehydration can lead to fatigue, mood swings, and difficulty focusing, which can all hinder cognitive performance. By staying hydrated with water, you can prevent dehydration and boost mental clarity, concentration, and overall brain health.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item3_Screen_5_title">Improved Kidney Function</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item3_Screen_5_des">Drinking water supports kidney health by helping to flush out waste products through urine. By replacing sugary drinks with water, you assist your body’s natural detoxification process, promoting better kidney function and overall well-being.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item3_Screen_6_title">Improved Heart Function</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item3_Screen_6_des">Choosing water over sugary beverages can lower the risk of heart disease and help reduce blood pressure. Staying hydrated also promotes better blood flow and enhances the elasticity of blood vessels—both essential for maintaining a healthy heart.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item3_Screen_7_title">Save Money</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item3_Screen_7_des">Opting for tap water or using a filtration system is a budget-friendly alternative to purchasing bottled drinks. This not only helps you save money on your grocery bill but also reduces plastic waste, benefiting both your wallet and the environment.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item4_Opening_des">Have you ever wondered if there are any benefits to drinking water on an empty stomach? \n\nNo worries. The benefits and drawbacks of doing that and tips for optimal hydration are all included here. Let\'s check them out.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item4_Screen_1_title">Aid Digestion</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item4_Screen_1_des">Drinking water on an empty stomach can stimulate digestive enzymes, improving digestion and enhancing nutrient absorption. It may also help relieve constipation by promoting regular bowel movements.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item4_Screen_2_title">Boost Metabolism</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item4_Screen_2_des">Drinking water on an empty stomach can boost your metabolism by increasing the body’s energy expenditure, which can enhance weight loss and support overall health.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item4_Screen_3_title">Improve Skin Health</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item4_Screen_3_des">Drinking water on an empty stomach helps flush out toxins and impurities from the body, promoting clearer, brighter skin.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item4_Screen_4_title">Note the Drawbacks</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item4_Screen_4_des">While drinking water on an empty stomach offers many benefits, it can sometimes cause symptoms like bloating and nausea. Additionally, it may interfere with the effectiveness of certain medications.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item5_Opening_des">Lemon water is not only a refreshing drink but also has a positive impact on your body.\n\nLet’s explore the top benefits of incorporating lemon water into your daily routine.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item5_Screen_1_title">Improve Digestive Health</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item5_Screen_1_des">Lemons contain compounds that stimulate the production of digestive juices, which can help ease indigestion and bloating. \nThe citric acid in lemons also helps to break down food in your stomach and improve nutrient absorption.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item5_Screen_2_title">Maintain Mineral Balance</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item5_Screen_2_des">Lemon water is rich in minerals that are crucial for maintaining healthy bodily functions, including nerve and muscle function, blood pressure regulation, and bone health.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item5_Screen_3_title">Improve Eyesight</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item5_Screen_3_des">Lemons are rich in vitamin C and antioxidants, which help protect your eyes from damage caused by free radicals. Regularly drinking lemon water may also reduce the risk of age-related macular degeneration, a leading cause of vision loss.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item5_Screen_4_title">Make Skin Soft</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item5_Screen_4_des">The vitamin C in lemons boosts collagen production, which helps make your skin smoother and firmer. Drinking lemon water also aids in hydrating your skin, improving its overall appearance and texture.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item5_Screen_5_title">Support Liver Health</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item5_Screen_5_des">The compounds in lemons help detoxify your liver and improve its overall function. Regularly drinking lemon water can reduce the risk of liver disease and other liver-related issues.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item5_Screen_6_title">Boost Metabolism</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item5_Screen_6_des">The citric acid in lemons helps stimulate the production of enzymes involved in breaking down fats. This can boost your body’s ability to burn calories more efficiently, making it easier to maintain a healthy weight.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item5_Screen_7_title">Reduce Inflammation</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item5_Screen_7_des">Lemons contain anti-inflammatory properties that can help reduce inflammation in the body. Since inflammation is linked to various health issues, including arthritis, heart disease, and cancer, regularly drinking lemon water can support overall health by minimizing inflammation.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item5_Screen_8_title">Maintain pH Balance</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item5_Screen_8_des">Despite their acidic taste, lemons have an alkalizing effect on the body. Drinking lemon water can help neutralize excess acid, promoting a healthy pH balance.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item5_Screen_9_title">Reduce Coffee Cravings</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item5_Screen_9_des">Lemon water offers a natural energy boost without the need for caffeine. Drinking it in the morning can stimulate both your body and mind, giving you a refreshing pick-me-up to start your day.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item6_Opening_des">There’s a common misconception that drinking water during meals can disrupt digestion.\n\nIn reality, drinking water during meals can be a healthy habit. Keep reading to debunk this myth.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item6_Screen_1_title">What Happens to Food and Water in the Stomach?</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item6_Screen_1_des">Once food and liquids are swallowed, they enter the stomach, where they are mixed and broken down by stomach acid and digestive enzymes.\n\nThis mixture, known as chyme, then slowly moves into the small intestine, where nutrient absorption takes place.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item6_Screen_2_title">Break the Misbelief: Do Liquids Decrease Stomach Acidity?</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item6_Screen_2_des">No, the stomach has a powerful ability to regulate its acidity.\n\nLiquids won’t affect the speed of digestion either. The stomach and small intestine work together to control how quickly food and liquids are released and digested.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item6_Screen_3_title">Reduce Overeating</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item6_Screen_3_des">Drinking water during a meal can help reduce overeating by filling up the stomach and curbing hunger.\n\nThis is especially beneficial for those looking to manage their weight.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item6_Screen_4_title">Aid in Digestion</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item6_Screen_4_des">Water helps dissolve food and nutrients, making them easier for the body to absorb. It also softens stools and promotes regular bowel movements, helping to prevent constipation.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item6_Screen_5_title">Limit the Amount</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item6_Screen_5_des">Drinking too much water during a meal can overfill your stomach. A few sips of water should be sufficient to aid digestion without overwhelming your stomach.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item6_Screen_6_title">Avoid Chilled Water</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item6_Screen_6_des">Drinking chilled water during a meal can slow down digestion. It\'s better to opt for room temperature or warm water to support optimal digestive function.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item6_Screen_7_title">Drink Water Before and After a Meal</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item6_Screen_7_des">Drinking water before and after meals helps keep you hydrated and promotes optimal digestion.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item7_Opening_des">Curious about how water improves your health in various ways?\n\nIn this article, we’ll explore the numerous health benefits of drinking water, helping you optimize your intake for a healthier you.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item7_Screen_1_title">Regulate Body Temperature</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item7_Screen_1_des">When we sweat, our bodies release heat, and water helps cool us down by evaporating from the skin.\n\nThis is why it’s crucial to drink water before, during, and after exercise to prevent dehydration and overheating.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item7_Screen_2_title">Aid in Digestion</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item7_Screen_2_des">Water helps dissolve food and nutrients, making them easier for the body to absorb. It also softens stools, which facilitates smoother bowel movements and helps prevent constipation.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item7_Screen_3_title">Flush Out Toxins</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item7_Screen_3_des">Water helps transport nutrients and oxygen to cells and organs while also carrying away waste and toxins. To support the body\'s natural detoxification processes, it\'s essential to drink enough water.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item7_Screen_4_title">Enhance Brain Function</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item7_Screen_4_des">Drinking water on an empty stomach helps keep the brain hydrated, improving cognitive function, focus, and overall mental clarity.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item7_Screen_5_title">Promote Healthy Skin</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item7_Screen_5_des">Water hydrates the skin, helping to maintain its elasticity and suppleness. When we’re dehydrated, our skin can become dry, tight, and flaky, leading to wrinkles and fine lines.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item7_Screen_6_title">Relieve Headaches</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item7_Screen_6_des">Dehydration is a common cause of headaches, and drinking water helps rehydrate the body, alleviating the symptoms.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item7_Screen_7_title">Increase Energy</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item7_Screen_7_des">Dehydration can lead to fatigue and reduced physical performance, impacting daily activities. Staying hydrated by drinking water has been shown to improve energy levels and reduce fatigue, whether you\'re active or sedentary.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item7_Screen_8_title">Support Weight Loss</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item7_Screen_8_des">Water can help fill us up and suppress appetite, making it easier to stick to a healthy diet. Additionally, it can boost metabolism and increase the number of calories burned.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item8_Opening_des">You might think that drinking plenty of water all the time is always beneficial, but there\'s a risk of overdoing it.\n\nOverhydration, or drinking too much water, can lead to serious health problems. Keep reading to learn more about the potential risks.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item8_Screen_1_title">Causes of Overhydration</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item8_Screen_1_des">- Drinking excessive amounts of water, especially during exercise or physical activities.\n- Consuming high amounts of electrolytes, such as sodium or potassium, without drinking enough water.\n- Certain medical conditions, such as heart, liver, or kidney disease, can disrupt the body\'s water balance.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item8_Screen_2_title">Overhydration\'s Risks</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item8_Screen_2_des">Overhydration can cause hyponatremia, a condition that leads to headaches, nausea, vomiting, confusion, seizures, and, in severe cases, coma or death.\n\nIt can also strain the kidneys, cause water retention, and lead to swelling in various body parts, resulting in discomfort, bloating, and other health issues.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item8_Screen_3_title">Who Is Vulnerable to Hyponatremia?</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item8_Screen_3_des">- Athletes and individuals who engage in intense exercise\n- Infants and children\n- The elderly with reduced kidney function\n- People with certain conditions that affect fluid balance in the body\n- Individuals taking medications that increase urine production\n- People who drink large amounts of water in a short period of time</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item8_Screen_4_title">Symptoms of Overhydration</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item8_Screen_4_des">Symptoms of overhydration may include headaches, nausea, vomiting, confusion, fatigue, muscle weakness and cramps, seizures, and even coma.\n\nThese symptoms can develop quickly and may be life-threatening in severe cases.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item8_Screen_5_title">How Much Water Is Too Much?</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item8_Screen_5_des">The amount of water a person needs can vary depending on several factors.\n\nTo avoid overhydration, you can use our app to determine your personal water needs, especially if you\'re engaging in exercise or activities that cause heavy sweating.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item8_Screen_6_title">Prevention of Overhydration</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item8_Screen_6_des">It’s important to monitor your fluid intake, especially during physical activities, and maintain a healthy balance of electrolytes in the body.\n\nIf you have a medical condition that affects water balance, work with your healthcare provider to manage the condition and prevent overhydration.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item8_Screen_7_title">Treatment of Overhydration</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item8_Screen_7_des">The treatment for overhydration depends on the severity of the condition and the underlying cause.\n\nIn mild cases, reducing fluid intake may be sufficient, while more severe cases could require hospitalization and treatment with intravenous fluids and medications to restore electrolyte balance.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item9_Opening_des">Parents always want to ensure their babies are well-cared for, but giving babies water can be harmful.\n\nRead on to learn more about the risks and why it’s important to avoid giving water to infants.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item9_Screen_1_title">How Water is Processed by the Kidneys</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item9_Screen_1_des">Water plays a crucial role in maintaining the balance of fluids and electrolytes in our bodies.\n\nThe kidneys are responsible for regulating this balance by filtering excess fluids and waste products from our blood and excreting them as urine.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item9_Screen_2_title">When Can Babies Start Drinking Water?</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item9_Screen_2_des">Babies can begin drinking small amounts of water after they are six months old and have started eating solid foods.\n\nIt\'s generally recommended to wait until the baby is one year old before introducing juice.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item9_Screen_3_title">Water Intoxication</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item9_Screen_3_des">Babies have small stomachs and can only handle a limited amount of fluid at once.\n\nGiving them too much water can dilute their blood and lead to a condition called water intoxication, or hyponatremia. This can cause serious health issues, including seizures, brain damage, and even death.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item9_Screen_4_title">Disrupt Nutrient Intake</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item9_Screen_4_des">Breast milk or formula provides all the essential nutrients babies need during their first six months of life.\n\nGiving babies water can fill their stomachs and reduce their appetite for milk, potentially leading to malnutrition and weight loss.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item9_Screen_5_title">Increase Risk of Infections</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item9_Screen_5_des">The risk of infections can increase, particularly if the water is not properly sterilized.\n\nWater may contain harmful bacteria and viruses that can lead to diarrhea and other illnesses in babies.</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item9_Screen_6_title">Upset Electrolyte Balance</string>
    <string name="Wd_Item9_Screen_6_des">Water lacks the necessary electrolytes that babies need to maintain their fluid balance.\n\nGiving babies water can disrupt their electrolyte balance and potentially lead to dehydration.</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item1_Opening_des">To reap the full benefits of water for your skin, following a consistent drinking schedule is key. Here are some tips to get you started:</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item1_Screen_1_title">Start Your Day With a Glass of Water</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item1_Screen_1_des">Kickstart your day by drinking a glass of water before breakfast. This helps hydrate your body and gives your skin a fresh start.</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item1_Screen_2_title">Drink Water Before and After Meals</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item1_Screen_2_des">Drinking water before meals helps you feel fuller, preventing overeating. It also aids digestion, which is beneficial for skin health. After meals, water helps flush out toxins and keeps your skin hydrated. Aim for at least one glass of water after each meal.</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item1_Screen_3_title">Drink Water During and After Exercise</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item1_Screen_3_des">Exercise causes your body to lose water through sweat, so it’s essential to replenish fluids to keep your skin hydrated and prevent wrinkles. Make sure to drink water during and after your workout to stay hydrated and support your skin health.</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item1_Screen_4_title">Drink Water Throughout the Day</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item1_Screen_4_des">Listening to your body’s thirst signals is key to staying properly hydrated. Keep a water bottle handy throughout the day, and drink whenever you feel thirsty to maintain optimal hydration levels for healthy, glowing skin.</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item1_Screen_5_title">Drink Water Before Bed</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item1_Screen_5_des">Drinking water before bed helps hydrate your body while you sleep, supporting skin health. As your skin cells regenerate and repair themselves overnight, staying hydrated is crucial for optimal skin recovery.</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item1_Screen_6_title">Limit Your Intake of Beverages That Can Dehydrate Your Skin</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item1_Screen_6_des">Beverages like alcohol and caffeine can dehydrate your skin, leading to wrinkles and other signs of aging. To maintain healthy, hydrated skin, limit your intake of these drinks and make sure to drink water in between.</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item2_Opening_des">Juices are a delicious and effective way to deliver essential nutrients that support healthy, glowing skin. Here are some of the best juices to enhance your skin\'s radiance</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item2_Screen_1_title">Carrot Juice</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item2_Screen_1_des">Carrots are rich in vitamin A, which is crucial for maintaining healthy skin. Vitamin A helps reduce inflammation, promotes skin cell turnover, and improves skin texture. Additionally, carrot juice is packed with antioxidants that protect the skin from environmental damage.</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item2_Screen_2_title">Beetroot Juice</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item2_Screen_2_des">Beetroot is a powerhouse of antioxidants, vitamins, and minerals, especially vitamin C, which is essential for collagen production. Collagen helps maintain skin elasticity and prevents wrinkles and sagging, giving the skin a youthful appearance.</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item2_Screen_3_title">Pomegranate Juice</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item2_Screen_3_des">Pomegranate is packed with antioxidants, including Vitamin C and polyphenols, that shield the skin from UV damage, pollution, and other environmental stressors. It also contains ellagic acid, which helps prevent collagen breakdown, slowing down the aging process and promoting youthful skin</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item2_Screen_4_title">Aloe Vera Juice</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item2_Screen_4_des">Aloe vera is renowned for its skin-healing properties. Aloe vera juice is rich in vitamins, minerals, and antioxidants that help soothe inflammation, promote skin repair, and enhance skin elasticity, making it an excellent choice for glowing, youthful skin.</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item2_Screen_5_title">Lemon Juice</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item2_Screen_5_des">Lemons are packed with Vitamin C, a powerful antioxidant that boosts collagen production, brightens the skin, and evens out skin tone. Lemon juice also has astringent properties, helping to tighten pores, control excess oil production, and prevent acne.</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item2_Screen_6_title">Green Juice</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item2_Screen_6_des">Green juices are rich in vitamins A, C, and E, all essential for healthy skin. They also contain chlorophyll, which helps detoxify the skin and promote overall skin health, giving it a radiant and refreshed appearance.</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item2_Screen_7_title">Apple Juice</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item2_Screen_7_des">Apple juice is packed with vitamins and minerals that nourish and hydrate the skin. It also promotes collagen production, which enhances skin elasticity and firmness, helping to maintain a youthful appearance.</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item2_Screen_8_title">Cucumber Juice</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item2_Screen_8_des">Cucumber juice is loaded with vitamins and minerals, and its high water content helps hydrate the skin and reduce inflammation. It can also help reduce dark circles under the eyes, promoting a refreshed and youthful look.</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item3_Opening_des">Drinking water and applying hot or cold water to your skin can both enhance its health and appearance. Each temperature has its unique benefits for your skin.</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item3_Screen_1_title">Benefits of Cold Water</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item3_Screen_1_des">Cold water helps reduce inflammation, puffiness, and redness in the skin. It can also minimize the appearance of pores, tighten the skin, and soothe irritated skin, making it particularly beneficial for conditions like eczema or rosacea.</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item3_Screen_2_title">Benefits of Hot Water</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item3_Screen_2_des">Hot water helps relax sore muscles and open up pores, making it easier to remove impurities and toxins from the skin. It can be especially beneficial for those dealing with stress-related skin conditions like acne, psoriasis, and eczema.</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item3_Screen_3_title">Pore Tightening</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item3_Screen_3_des">Combining cold and hot water can offer additional benefits. Rinsing your face with cold water helps tighten and minimize pores while soothing inflammation and redness, making it ideal for sensitive skin. On the other hand, warm water opens up pores, allowing for the removal of impurities and deep cleansing.</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item3_Screen_4_title">Blood Circulation</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item3_Screen_4_des">Alternating between hot and cold water can boost blood circulation in the skin. Hot water increases blood flow, promoting a healthy glow, while cold water reduces inflammation and puffiness, helping to rejuvenate the skin.</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item3_Screen_5_title">Increased Skin Elasticity</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item3_Screen_5_des">Cold water helps tighten the skin, reducing the appearance of fine lines and wrinkles. Hot water, on the other hand, boosts blood circulation, promoting better skin elasticity and a more youthful look.</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item3_Screen_6_title">Relaxation</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item3_Screen_6_des">Both hot and cold water can help reduce stress and promote relaxation. Hot water soothes sore muscles and induces calm, while cold water invigorates and energizes the body, offering a refreshing boost.</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item4_Opening_des">Did you know that drinking water can play a role in promoting hair growth? It\'s true! Here’s how staying hydrated can support healthy, growing hair.</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item4_Screen_1_title">Keep Your Hair and Scalp Hydrated</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item4_Screen_1_des">Adequate water intake helps keep your hair moisturized, reducing the risk of dryness that can lead to breakage and hair loss. It also aids in preventing an itchy, irritated scalp, which is a common cause of dandruff.</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item4_Screen_2_title">Promote Scalp Circulation</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item4_Screen_2_des">Drinking sufficient water helps increase blood volume, which in turn promotes healthy blood flow to the scalp. This improved circulation nourishes the hair follicles, supporting strong and healthy hair growth.</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item4_Screen_3_title">Aid in Nutrient Absorption</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item4_Screen_3_des">Drinking enough water is crucial for the proper absorption of nutrients, including those necessary for healthy hair growth. Dehydration can hinder nutrient absorption, leading to weak, brittle hair that is more susceptible to breakage.</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item4_Screen_4_title">Prevent Hair Damage</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item4_Screen_4_des">Dry hair is more susceptible to breakage and damage. Staying hydrated helps keep your hair moisturized, preventing dryness and reducing the risk of damage and breakage.</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item4_Screen_5_title">Help Detoxify Your Body</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item4_Screen_5_des">Drinking enough water aids in flushing out toxins from your body, which can improve the health of your hair and scalp. A cleaner, toxin-free body contributes to stronger, healthier hair.</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item4_Screen_6_title">Tips for Drinking Enough Water for Hair Growth</string>
    <string name="Bs_Item4_Screen_6_des">- Carry a water bottle with you to easily track your water intake.\n- Add natural flavorings, like lemon or mint, if you find plain water difficult to drink.\n- Incorporate water-rich foods, like watermelon, cucumbers, and strawberries, into your diet.\n- Limit dehydrating beverages, such as alcohol and caffeine, to maintain hydration levels.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item1_Opening_des">Tired of tossing and turning all night, struggling to get restful sleep? You\'re not alone.\n\nFortunately, we’ll explore some of the most effective and delicious drinks to help you achieve the restful night’s sleep you deserve.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item1_Screen_1_title">Chamomile Tea</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item1_Screen_1_des">Chamomile is well-known for its calming properties. It contains antioxidants that help to relax the body and mind, making it an ideal beverage to drink before bedtime to promote better sleep.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item1_Screen_2_title">Warm Milk</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item1_Screen_2_des">Warm milk is known for its sleep-promoting benefits. It contains tryptophan, an amino acid that supports the production of melatonin, a hormone that helps regulate your sleep patterns. Additionally, the calcium in milk helps the brain utilize tryptophan more effectively, contributing to a restful night’s sleep.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item1_Screen_3_title">Tart Cherry Juice</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item1_Screen_3_des">Tart cherries are naturally rich in melatonin, the hormone responsible for regulating sleep-wake cycles. Drinking tart cherry juice before bed can help boost melatonin levels, leading to improved sleep quality.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item1_Screen_4_title">Coconut Water</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item1_Screen_4_des">Coconut water is a natural source of magnesium, a mineral known for its ability to relax the body and improve sleep quality. It also contains potassium, which helps regulate blood pressure and promotes muscle relaxation, contributing to a restful night’s sleep.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item1_Screen_5_title">Nutmeg Tea</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item1_Screen_5_des">Nutmeg contains a natural sedative called myristicin, which can help calm your mind and reduce anxiety. To make nutmeg tea, simply simmer a cup of water with a pinch of nutmeg for about 10 minutes, and enjoy the relaxing benefits before bedtime.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item1_Screen_6_title">Banana Tea</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item1_Screen_6_des">Banana tea contains potassium and magnesium, which are natural muscle relaxants, along with the amino acid tryptophan, known for its ability to induce sleep. To make banana tea, simply cut off the ends of a ripe banana and place it in boiling water for about 10 minutes. Enjoy the soothing benefits before bedtime.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item1_Screen_7_title">Decaffeinated Green Tea</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item1_Screen_7_des">Green tea contains an amino acid called L-theanine, which promotes relaxation and reduces stress. Drinking decaffeinated green tea before bed can help calm the mind and promote better sleep, without the stimulating effects of caffeine.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item2_Opening_des">While drinking alcohol can be enjoyable, it\'s important to consider how it affects your body. This article explores the various ways alcohol can impact your health, helping you make informed decisions about your drinking habits and overall well-being.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item2_Screen_1_title">Immediate Effects of Alcohol</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item2_Screen_1_des">- Slurred speech\n- Impaired motor skills and coordination\n- Nausea and vomiting\n- Decreased inhibitions\n- Memory lapses or blackouts</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item2_Screen_2_title">Liver Damage</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item2_Screen_2_des">Chronic alcohol consumption can cause severe and potentially life-threatening damage to the liver. The liver plays a crucial role in processing and filtering alcohol from the bloodstream. However, excessive drinking can overwhelm this function and lead to conditions like cirrhosis, fatty liver disease, and alcoholic hepatitis, which can severely affect liver function and overall health.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item2_Screen_3_title">Increased Cancer Risk</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item2_Screen_3_des">Chronic and heavy alcohol consumption has been linked to a higher risk of developing various cancers, including breast, liver, colon, and esophageal cancer. Alcohol can cause damage to cells and tissues in the body, leading to inflammation and changes in DNA that increase cancer risk. It\'s important to limit alcohol intake to reduce these risks.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item2_Screen_4_title">Cardiovascular Disease</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item2_Screen_4_des">Chronic alcohol consumption can have a negative impact on heart health. It increases the risk of developing high blood pressure, heart disease, stroke, and other cardiovascular issues. Excessive drinking can weaken the heart muscle and lead to arrhythmias, irregular heartbeats, and even heart failure over time. Limiting alcohol intake is essential for maintaining a healthy heart.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item2_Screen_5_title">Poor Sleep</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item2_Screen_5_des">While alcohol might initially make you feel sleepy, it actually disrupts sleep patterns. It can cause frequent awakenings throughout the night and reduce the quality of restorative sleep. As a result, you may wake up feeling groggy, fatigued, or less refreshed in the morning. Regular alcohol consumption can lead to chronic sleep disturbances over time.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item2_Screen_6_title">Weakened Immune System</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item2_Screen_6_des">Excessive alcohol consumption can impair the body’s immune response by reducing the production of white blood cells, which are crucial for defending against infections. Chronic drinking can also cause inflammation throughout the body, further weakening the immune system. As a result, regular heavy drinking makes the body more susceptible to illnesses and infections.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item3_Opening_des">When seeking support for your mental well-being, don\'t overlook the power of natural remedies. Explore the best herbal teas that can help promote calmness and balance, allowing you to stay centered amidst life\'s challenges.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item3_Screen_1_title">Chamomile Tea</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item3_Screen_1_des">Chamomile contains compounds that bind to the same brain receptors as Valium, helping to calm the nervous system and promote restful sleep.\n\nSuggested intake: Use 1 tablespoon (2g) of dried chamomile flowers per cup of water. Drink 1-2 cups daily. Avoid if you have severe allergies, take blood thinners, are pregnant, or are giving it to infants or young children.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item3_Screen_2_title">Lavender Tea</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item3_Screen_2_des">Lavender is well-known for its soothing properties and is often used to treat anxiety, depression, and insomnia. The aroma of lavender helps promote relaxation, reduce stress, and improve mood.\nSuggested intake: Use 2 teaspoons (about 1.5 grams) of dried lavender flowers per cup of water. Drink 1-2 cups per day, preferably before bedtime.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item3_Screen_3_title">Lemon Balm Tea</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item3_Screen_3_des">Lemon balm, a member of the mint family, is known for its calming effects. It helps reduce stress levels and can improve cognitive function, making it a great choice for mental well-being.\n\nSuggested intake: Use 1 tablespoon (about 2 grams) of dried lemon balm leaves per cup of water. Drink 1-3 cups per day, ideally in the morning or afternoon.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item3_Screen_4_title">Passionflower Tea</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item3_Screen_4_des">Passionflower is known for its calming effects, helping to reduce anxiety and promote better sleep. It is made by steeping dried passionflower leaves and flowers in hot water.\n\nSuggested intake: Use 1 tablespoon (about 2 grams) of dried passionflower per cup of water. Drink 1 cup per day, preferably in the evening before bed.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item3_Screen_5_title">Green Tea</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item3_Screen_5_des">Green tea is rich in L-theanine, an amino acid that promotes relaxation and reduces anxiety, while also improving cognitive function.\n\nSuggested intake: Use 1 teaspoon (about 2 grams) of green tea leaves per cup of water. Drink 2-3 cups per day, preferably in the morning or early afternoon. It\'s not advised to consume more than 6-8 cups daily.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item3_Screen_6_title">Rose Tea</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item3_Screen_6_des">Rose tea is renowned for its calming effects, helping to reduce anxiety, improve mood, and promote relaxation. It\'s also beneficial for overall emotional well-being.\n\nSuggested intake: For fresh petals, boil 2 cups of petals with 3 cups (700 ml) of water for 5 minutes, then strain. For dried petals, steep 1 tablespoon per cup in boiling water for 10-20 minutes. Be sure to check brand guidelines for specific instructions.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item3_Screen_7_title">Ginger Tea</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item3_Screen_7_des">Ginger tea has warming and\nstimulating properties that can help\nreduce stress, anxiety, and mental\nfatigue. It also has anti-inflammatory\nbenefits that support overall health.\nSuggested intake: Use about a\none-inch piece of ginger per cup of\ntea, and drink 1-2 cups per day.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item4_Opening_des">Stress and anxiety are issues that many people experience, but there\'s a simple and effective way to help calm your mind: drinking water. Learn how staying hydrated can help reduce stress and promote a sense of calm.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item4_Screen_1_title">The Link Between Dehydration and Anxiety</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item4_Screen_1_des">Dehydration can worsen anxiety symptoms, increasing feelings of tension and fatigue.\nIt impacts both the body and brain, causing changes in mood, cognition, and overall functioning.\nWhen dehydrated, the body releases stress hormones, which can exacerbate anxiety symptoms such as heart palpitations and rapid breathing.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item4_Screen_2_title">Regulate Cortisol Levels</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item4_Screen_2_des">Cortisol is a hormone released in response to stress. When dehydrated, cortisol levels can rise, making us more susceptible to stress and anxiety.\n\nDrinking water helps regulate cortisol levels, leading to a reduction in stress and anxiety.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item4_Screen_3_title">Improve Mood</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item4_Screen_3_des">Even mild dehydration can lead to irritability, fatigue, and difficulty concentrating.\n\nBy staying hydrated, we can help stabilize our mood and avoid unnecessary stress.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item4_Screen_4_title">Better Sleep</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item4_Screen_4_des">Improved hydration can enhance sleep quality, which in turn helps reduce stress levels. When well-hydrated, we are less likely to experience common sleep disturbances like snoring and sleep apnea, leading to a more restful night.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item4_Screen_5_title">Practice Mindful Hydration</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item4_Screen_5_des">\nDrinking water can be a mindful practice, allowing us to stay present and calm in the moment. By focusing on the sensation of drinking and being fully aware, we shift away from mindlessly consuming it. This intentional practice can promote relaxation and contribute to stress reduction.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item5_Opening_des">If you\'re seeking a natural solution to help alleviate stress and anxiety, drinking milk before bed might be just what you need. In this article, we\'ll explore why this simple remedy can be an effective way to unwind and promote relaxation</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item5_Screen_1_title">Milk Contains Tryptophan</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item5_Screen_1_des">Milk is a natural source of tryptophan, an amino acid that plays a crucial role in the production of serotonin. Serotonin is known as the \"feel-good\" hormone, as it helps promote feelings of happiness, relaxation, and well-being, which can reduce stress and anxiety.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item5_Screen_2_title">Milk Contains Calcium</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item5_Screen_2_des">Calcium is essential for maintaining a healthy nervous system. It helps regulate the release of neurotransmitters and hormones, which can have a calming effect on the body. This contributes to reducing anxiety and promoting a sense of tranquility.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item5_Screen_3_title">Milk Contains Magnesium</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item5_Screen_3_des">Magnesium is a vital mineral for proper nervous system function. It has been shown to promote muscle relaxation by reducing muscle tension and spasms, helping to alleviate stress and contribute to a calming effect on the body.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item5_Screen_4_title">Tips for Drinking Milk Before Bed</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item5_Screen_4_des">- The best time to drink milk is at bedtime to help relax your body and mind.\n- Drink milk at a lukewarm temperature for better digestion and comfort.\n- Consider adding a small amount of turmeric, black pepper, nutmeg powder, or jaifal for an extra calming effect.\n- If you experience coughing after drinking milk, try drinking warm water to soothe your throat.</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item5_Screen_5_title">Please note:</string>
    <string name="Sc_Item5_Screen_5_des">Milk contains lactose, which can be difficult for some people to digest. If you experience digestive issues after drinking milk, you may want to try a lactose-free alternative like almond milk, soy milk, or oat milk.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item1_Opening_des">Losing weight can be tough, but it doesn’t have to be bland. Enhance your journey with delicious and refreshing drinks that support fat burning.\n\nCheck out some of the best fat-burning beverages to help you reach your weight loss goals:</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item1_Screen_1_title">Green Tea</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item1_Screen_1_des">Green tea is packed with antioxidants that boost metabolism and support fat burning. Its polyphenols enhance fat oxidation, making it an excellent addition to your weight loss plan.\n\nAdditionally, the caffeine content in green tea provides an energy boost and can improve exercise performance, helping you stay active and burn more calories.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item1_Screen_2_title">"Coffee "</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item1_Screen_2_des">Coffee is a great source of caffeine, which has been shown to boost metabolism and promote fat oxidation, aiding in fat burning.\n\nTo maximize its benefits, opt for black coffee and avoid adding sugar or cream, as they can increase calorie intake and counteract your weight loss efforts.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item1_Screen_3_title">Apple Cider Vinegar</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item1_Screen_3_des">Apple cider vinegar is known to help curb appetite and enhance feelings of fullness, making it easier to manage your calorie intake.\n\nIt may also support fat burning and improve insulin sensitivity, contributing to better overall weight management.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item1_Screen_4_title">Lemon Water</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item1_Screen_4_des">Lemon water is a refreshing and nutrient-packed drink, rich in vitamin C, which strengthens the immune system and supports healthy digestion.\n\nIt also aids in detoxifying the liver and keeps you hydrated—both crucial for maintaining an efficient metabolism and overall well-being.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item1_Screen_5_title">Ginger Tea</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item1_Screen_5_des">Ginger tea is a powerful ally in weight loss, as it can help suppress appetite and support your fat-burning efforts.\n\nBy boosting metabolism and increasing energy expenditure, ginger tea can make it easier to shed unwanted pounds while keeping you energized throughout the day.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item1_Screen_6_title"><![CDATA[Cumin & Cinnamon Water]]></string>
    <string name="Hl_Item1_Screen_6_des">Cumin and cinnamon are spices known for their positive effects on weight loss and metabolism.\n\nTo prepare, add a teaspoon each of cumin and cinnamon to boiling water, let it steep for 5 minutes, then strain and enjoy this flavorful, metabolism-boosting drink.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item1_Screen_7_title">Chia and Lemon Water</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item1_Screen_7_des">Chia seeds are packed with fiber, protein, and healthy fats, making them a great addition to your weight loss routine. Lemon, a natural detoxifier, complements this drink by aiding digestion and boosting hydration.\n\nTo make it, mix 2 tablespoons of chia seeds with water, squeeze in the juice of half a lemon, and let it sit for 10 minutes before enjoying.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item1_Screen_8_title">Protein Shakes</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item1_Screen_8_des">Protein is vital for building and maintaining muscle mass, which plays a key role in boosting metabolism.\n\nIncluding a protein shake in your diet can help increase your protein intake, reduce appetite, and support your weight loss efforts. Opt for low-sugar, high-quality protein powders for the best results.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item2_Opening_des">Fasting has gained popularity in recent years for its numerous health benefits. However, staying hydrated and managing hunger pangs can be challenging during fasting periods.\n\nHere’s a helpful guide to drinks that can support you while fasting, keeping you hydrated and making the experience more manageable.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item2_Screen_1_title">Water</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item2_Screen_1_des">Water is the top choice during a fast because it’s calorie-free and doesn’t impact insulin levels.\n\nStaying hydrated with water not only helps reduce hunger pangs but also aids in preventing overeating when it’s time to break your fast. It’s essential for maintaining overall health during fasting.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item2_Screen_2_title">Black Coffee</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item2_Screen_2_des">Black coffee is an excellent option during fasting, as it helps reduce hunger and provides an energy boost. The caffeine in coffee has been shown to increase metabolic rate and promote fat mobilization, which can be especially beneficial during extended fasts.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item2_Screen_3_title">Herbal Tea</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item2_Screen_3_des">Herbal teas, like peppermint, ginger, and chamomile, are soothing and can help you relax during a fast.\n\nThese teas offer additional benefits, such as reducing inflammation, aiding digestion, and promoting a sense of calm, making them a great choice for both physical and mental support while fasting</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item2_Screen_4_title">Lemon Water</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item2_Screen_4_des">Lemon water is a low-calorie option that helps detoxify the liver, support digestion, and boost the immune system. The citric acid in lemon water is believed to have alkalizing properties, helping to balance the body’s pH levels.\n\nHowever, it’s important to consume lemon water in moderation, as excessive acidity can have negative effects on your dental health and digestive system.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item2_Screen_5_title">Apple Cider Vinegar</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item2_Screen_5_des">Apple cider vinegar is known for its ability to help regulate blood sugar levels and improve insulin sensitivity. It’s also low in calories, making it an ideal option during fasting as it won’t break your fast.\n\nTo enjoy its benefits, mix one tablespoon of apple cider vinegar with water and sip it throughout your fasting period.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item3_Opening_des">Did you know that drinking water can support your weight loss efforts? It’s true! There are several effective tips you can follow to make the most of water for weight loss. Let’s explore how staying hydrated can help you achieve your goals.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item3_Screen_1_title">Start Your Day with Water</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item3_Screen_1_des">Drinking a glass of water as soon as you wake up helps kickstart your metabolism and prepares your body for the day ahead. It’s a simple yet powerful way to boost hydration and energy first thing in the morning.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item3_Screen_2_title">Stay Hydrated Throughout the Day</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item3_Screen_2_des">Use our app as a water intake calculator and smart reminder to stay on track with your hydration goals. Staying hydrated helps you feel full, reducing the chances of overeating and supporting your weight loss efforts.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item3_Screen_3_title">Drink Water Before Meals</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item3_Screen_3_des">Drinking 16 ounces of water about 30 minutes before meals can help reduce hunger and prevent overeating.\n\nIt also helps you feel fuller, which can naturally reduce calorie intake and support your weight loss goals.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item3_Screen_4_title">Replace Sugary Drinks with Water</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item3_Screen_4_des">Sugary drinks like soda and juice are packed with empty calories and can contribute to weight gain.\n\nBy swapping these beverages for water, you can save hundreds of calories each day and support your weight loss efforts.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item3_Screen_5_title">Drink When Feeling Hungry</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item3_Screen_5_des">Sometimes, thirst is mistaken for hunger, leading to unnecessary eating.\n\nIf you’re feeling hungry, try drinking a glass of water first. It can help you feel fuller and reduce unnecessary calorie intake. If you\'re still hungry afterward, opt for a healthy snack or meal.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item3_Screen_6_title">Drink Water Throughout Your Workout</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item3_Screen_6_des">Staying hydrated during exercise is essential for optimal performance and recovery.\n\nBe sure to drink water before, during, and after your workout to maintain energy levels, prevent dehydration, and support muscle recovery.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item3_Screen_7_title">Add Flavor to Your Water</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item3_Screen_7_des">If plain water feels boring, try adding natural flavors like lemon, lime, or cucumber.\n\nThese additions can make water more enjoyable and help you increase your daily water intake.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item3_Screen_8_title">Keep Water Handy</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item3_Screen_8_des">Keep a water bottle with you at all times to make it easier to stay hydrated throughout the day. This not only promotes hydration but also helps reduce appetite and prevent overeating.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item4_Opening_des">Have you ever noticed people carrying a water bottle during their workout?\n\nProper hydration plays a crucial role in exercise performance. Read on to discover how staying hydrated can enhance your workout and overall fitness.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item4_Screen_1_title">Increase Athletic Performance</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item4_Screen_1_des">Dehydration can lead to fatigue, cramps, and reduced endurance, all of which negatively affect athletic performance.\n\nStaying hydrated helps the body regulate temperature and maintain electrolyte balance, both of which are essential for optimal performance during exercise.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item4_Screen_2_title">Reduce Risk of Heat Illness</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item4_Screen_2_des">Dehydration impairs your body’s ability to regulate temperature, increasing the risk of heat exhaustion or even heatstroke.\n\nStaying hydrated helps maintain your body’s temperature regulation, reducing the chances of heat-related illnesses during exercise or in hot conditions.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item4_Screen_3_title">Improve Recovery</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item4_Screen_3_des">Water plays a key role in transporting nutrients to cells and removing waste products, both of which are crucial for recovery after exercise.\n\nStaying hydrated post-workout helps reduce muscle soreness and accelerates recovery time, allowing you to get back to your routine more quickly.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item4_Screen_4_title">Improve Cognitive Function</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item4_Screen_4_des">Dehydration can impair cognitive performance, affecting decision-making and reaction time.\n\nStaying hydrated helps maintain mental clarity and focus, ensuring athletes stay sharp and perform their best during exercise.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item4_Screen_5_title">Optimal Fluid Intake</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item4_Screen_5_des">Optimal fluid intake during exercise varies based on factors such as body weight, workout intensity, and duration.\n\nUse our app to estimate how much water you need to drink to replenish the fluids lost during exercise and stay properly hydrated.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item5_Opening_des">Have you ever found it difficult to eat, talk, or drink because of a sore throat?\n\nLuckily, certain drinks with antibacterial, anti-inflammatory, and antioxidant properties can provide relief. Let’s take a look at some of the best options to help soothe your sore throat.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item5_Screen_1_title">Warm Water with Honey and Lemon</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item5_Screen_1_des">Warm water can help ease throat discomfort, while honey, with its natural antibacterial properties, coats and soothes the throat.\n\nLemon provides a boost to the immune system and adds an extra layer of relief, making this combination a soothing remedy for a sore throat.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item5_Screen_2_title">Ginger Tea</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item5_Screen_2_des">Ginger has natural anti-inflammatory properties that can help reduce throat pain and irritation.\n\nAdditionally, it acts as an expectorant, helping to break up mucus and clear the throat, providing relief from congestion and discomfort.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item5_Screen_3_title">Peppermint Tea</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item5_Screen_3_des">Peppermint has natural cooling properties that can help numb the throat and reduce pain and irritation.\n\nIt’s a soothing remedy that can provide relief and promote relaxation, making it ideal for a sore throat.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item5_Screen_4_title">Turmeric Milk</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item5_Screen_4_des">Turmeric is known for its anti-inflammatory and infection-fighting properties.\n\nTo make this soothing drink, heat a cup of milk and add a teaspoon of turmeric powder, a pinch of black pepper, and a tablespoon of honey for sweetness. This combination helps reduce throat inflammation and promotes healing.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item5_Screen_5_title">Orange Tea</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item5_Screen_5_des">Oranges are packed with vitamin C, which helps boost the immune system and reduce inflammation.\n\nTo make this refreshing tea, slice an orange and add it to a pot of boiling water with a few fresh peppermint leaves. Let it steep for 10-15 minutes before straining and serving for a soothing, immune-boosting drink.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item5_Screen_6_title">Warm Salt Water</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item5_Screen_6_des">Although not a traditional drink, gargling with warm salt water is a simple and effective way to soothe a sore throat.\n\nSalt helps reduce inflammation and draw out excess fluid from the throat, which can alleviate pain and discomfort.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item5_Screen_7_title">Apple Cider Vinegar and Honey</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item5_Screen_7_des">Apple cider vinegar has antibacterial and antiviral properties, while honey helps coat and soothe the throat.\n\nMix a tablespoon of apple cider vinegar and honey into a cup of warm water for a soothing, antibacterial drink that can help alleviate throat discomfort.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item5_Screen_8_title">Herbal Tea</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item5_Screen_8_des">Various herbal teas can be effective in soothing a sore throat. Chamomile, slippery elm, and licorice root are all excellent choices.\n\nThese herbs have calming and anti-inflammatory properties that can help relieve throat discomfort and promote healing.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item6_Opening_des">Stomach bloating can be caused by various factors and, while common, it can be uncomfortable and even painful.\n\nHere are some drinks that can help provide relief from bloating:</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item6_Screen_1_title">Peppermint Tea</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item6_Screen_1_des">Peppermint has natural calming properties that can help reduce bloating and relieve gas.\n\nDrinking peppermint tea can also relax the muscles in the digestive tract, promoting better digestion and easing discomfort.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item6_Screen_2_title">Ginger Tea</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item6_Screen_2_des">Ginger is a natural anti-inflammatory that can help reduce bloating and stomach discomfort.\n\nDrinking ginger tea aids in digestion and helps prevent constipation, both of which can contribute to bloating.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item6_Screen_3_title">Fennel Tea</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item6_Screen_3_des">Fennel acts as a natural diuretic, helping to reduce water retention in the body, which can cause bloating.\n\nAdditionally, fennel tea stimulates digestion and helps relieve gas, providing relief from bloating and discomfort.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item6_Screen_4_title">Lemon Water</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item6_Screen_4_des">Lemon is a natural diuretic that helps flush excess water out of the body, reducing bloating.\n\nDrinking lemon water can also promote better digestion and reduce inflammation in the stomach, providing relief from discomfort.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item6_Screen_5_title">Chamomile Tea</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item6_Screen_5_des">Chamomile is a natural anti-inflammatory that can help relax the muscles in the digestive tract.\n\nThis relaxation can reduce bloating and discomfort, providing relief and promoting better digestion.</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item6_Screen_6_title">Water</string>
    <string name="Hl_Item6_Screen_6_des">Staying hydrated is key to preventing and reducing bloating.\n\nDrinking plenty of water helps flush out excess sodium and toxins from the body, which can contribute to bloating and discomfort.</string>
    <string name="cardio_vascular_health_title_1">Drink Water for Healthy Blood Sugar</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item1_Opening_des">Did you know that drinking water can help promote healthy blood sugar levels?\n\nRead on to learn how staying hydrated can support the regulation of blood sugar:</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item1_Screen_1_title">Dehydration and High Blood Sugar</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item1_Screen_1_des">When the body is dehydrated, blood sugar levels can become more concentrated, potentially leading to hyperglycemia (high blood sugar).\n\nIn addition, dehydration triggers the release of vasopressin, a hormone that signals the liver to produce more glucose, further raising blood sugar levels.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item1_Screen_2_title">Water Flushes Out Excess Sugar</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item1_Screen_2_des">When blood sugar levels are high, the kidneys work harder to remove excess sugar from the body.\n\nDrinking plenty of water helps your kidneys function more efficiently, flushing out excess sugar and preventing it from accumulating in the bloodstream.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item1_Screen_3_title">Water Promotes Weight Loss</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item1_Screen_3_des">Drinking water before and after meals can help you feel fuller, reducing the likelihood of overeating and blood sugar spikes.\n\nBeing overweight or obese can make it harder for your body to produce and use insulin effectively, contributing to higher blood sugar levels.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item1_Screen_4_title">Water Improves Insulin Sensitivity</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item1_Screen_4_des">When you\'re dehydrated, your body produces more stress hormones, which can reduce insulin sensitivity. Staying well-hydrated helps to improve insulin sensitivity, making it easier for your body to process glucose and regulate blood sugar levels. Proper hydration supports better metabolic function and helps prevent insulin resistance.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item1_Screen_5_title">Notice the Quality of Water</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item1_Screen_5_des">Drinking water with high mineral content, such as magnesium and calcium, can improve insulin sensitivity and reduce the risk of developing type 2 diabetes. These minerals play a vital role in regulating glucose metabolism, and choosing mineral-rich water can provide added benefits for blood sugar control and overall health.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item1_Screen_6_title">What Is Normal Blood Sugar Level?</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item1_Screen_6_des">For adults without diabetes, normal blood sugar levels are as follows:\n• Before meals or when fasting: 4.0 to 5.4 mmol/L (72 to 99 mg/dL)\n• At least 90 minutes after eating: Under 7.8 mmol/L (140 mg/dL)\n\nMaintaining these levels helps ensure that the body\'s metabolism and insulin production are functioning optimally. Regular monitoring is important for those at risk of or managing diabetes.</string>
    <string name="cardio_vascular_health_title_2">Best and Worst Drinks for Managing Diabetes</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item2_Opening_des">Maintaining stable blood sugar levels is essential for individuals with diabetes, and the drinks you consume can have a significant impact. \n\nDiscover the best and worst drinks for managing blood sugar and making healthier choices to support your overall health.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item2_Screen_1_title">Water: The Ideal Hydration Choice</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item2_Screen_1_des">Water is the best option for staying hydrated and regulating blood sugar levels. It contains no sugar or carbohydrates, making it an excellent choice for maintaining healthy blood sugar levels throughout the day.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item2_Screen_2_title">Tea: A Beneficial Option for Diabetics</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item2_Screen_2_des">Tea, especially green tea, is packed with antioxidants that may help reduce the risk of developing diabetes. Additionally, tea contains no calories or sugar, making it a great choice for diabetics looking to manage their blood sugar levels.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item2_Screen_3_title">Low-Fat Milk: A Healthy Option for Diabetics</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item2_Screen_3_des">Low-fat milk is a good choice for diabetics as it contains protein, calcium, and vitamin D while having a lower glycemic load compared to regular milk. This makes it a suitable beverage to help manage blood sugar levels.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item2_Screen_4_title">Sugary Drinks: The Worst Choice</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item2_Screen_4_des">Sugary drinks, such as soda, fruit juice, and energy drinks, are high in sugar and can lead to dangerous spikes in blood sugar levels. \n\nThey should be avoided by individuals with diabetes to help maintain healthy blood sugar control.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item2_Screen_5_title">Sugar-Free Drinks and Weight Gain</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item2_Screen_5_des">Many sugar-free drinks, such as diet sodas, contain artificial sweeteners. \n\nThese can contribute to weight gain, increased insulin resistance, and a higher risk of developing type 2 diabetes.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item2_Screen_6_title">Sports Drinks and Blood Sugar</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item2_Screen_6_des">Sports drinks often contain high levels of sugar, which can cause a rapid increase in blood sugar levels, making them harmful for diabetics.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item2_Screen_7_title">Sweetened Drinks and Blood Sugar</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item2_Screen_7_des">Sweetened tea, coffee drinks, and alcohol are high in sugar and calories, which can lead to blood sugar spikes and should be avoided by diabetics.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item2_Screen_8_title">Full-fat Milk and Diabetes</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item2_Screen_8_des">Full-fat milk contains more fat and calories compared to low-fat milk, and it has a higher glycemic load, which can worsen blood sugar control in diabetics.</string>
    <string name="cardio_vascular_health_title_3">Best Times to Drink Water for Heart Health</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item3_Opening_des">Water makes up about 60% of your body, and staying hydrated plays a key role in maintaining heart health. Drinking water at the right times can help reduce the risk of heart disease. \n\nLet’s explore the optimal times to drink water for promoting a healthy heart.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item3_Screen_1_title">Upon Waking</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item3_Screen_1_des">Drinking water right after waking up helps rehydrate your body after hours of sleep. It also supports heart health by reducing the risk of blood clots and boosting your metabolism, which can contribute to overall cardiovascular well-being.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item3_Screen_2_title">Before Meals</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item3_Screen_2_des">Drinking water before meals can help you feel fuller, which may reduce the amount of food you consume. This simple habit can prevent overeating and help manage weight, reducing the risk of obesity—a significant risk factor for heart disease.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item3_Screen_3_title">Between 6 a.m. and Noon</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item3_Screen_3_des">Most heart attacks occur in the morning, between 6 a.m. and noon, as the body’s stress hormone levels, blood pressure, and heart rate typically rise during this time. Drinking water can help regulate blood pressure and heart rate, potentially reducing the risk of heart-related events during these hours.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item3_Screen_4_title">During and After Exercise</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item3_Screen_4_des">Staying hydrated during and after exercise helps prevent dehydration, which can place additional stress on the heart. Drinking water during physical activity helps regulate body temperature, preventing overheating, and ensures proper blood flow, which can reduce the risk of heart palpitations.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item3_Screen_5_title">Before a Bath</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item3_Screen_5_des">Drinking water before a bath can help counteract the strain that warm water may place on the heart by regulating body temperature, heart rate, and blood pressure. \n\nWarm baths can sometimes cause dehydration, but staying hydrated beforehand can help prevent this and ensure that your body handles the temperature changes more effectively.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item3_Screen_6_title">Throughout the Day</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item3_Screen_6_des">Maintaining hydration throughout the day is essential for overall heart health. Drinking water regularly helps regulate blood pressure, prevents blood clots, and reduces the risk of heart disease. \n\nConsistent hydration ensures that your cardiovascular system functions optimally, promoting a healthy heart.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item3_Screen_7_title">Before Bedtime</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item3_Screen_7_des">Drinking a glass of water before bed can help prevent heart disease by reducing the risk of blood clots and heart attacks during sleep. \n\nIt also ensures your body stays hydrated overnight, supporting healthy circulation and overall heart function as you rest.</string>
    <string name="cardio_vascular_health_title_4">Caffeine\'s Effects on Heart Health</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item4_Opening_des">Caffeine is a widely consumed stimulant found in coffee, tea, energy drinks, and more. While it can offer a boost in energy and alertness, there are concerns regarding its effects on heart health. \n\nIn this article, we\'ll explore how caffeine affects the heart and what you should know to make informed choices about your consumption.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item4_Screen_1_title">Increase Blood Flow</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item4_Screen_1_des">When consumed in moderation, caffeine can benefit heart health by increasing blood flow. It stimulates the production of nitric oxide, which helps to dilate blood vessels, improving circulation and reducing the strain on the heart. This can promote overall cardiovascular health when consumed appropriately.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item4_Screen_2_title">Reduce Inflammation</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item4_Screen_2_des">Chronic inflammation is a significant risk factor for heart disease. Caffeine has been shown to help reduce inflammation in the body, which may lower the risk of developing cardiovascular conditions. By moderating inflammation, caffeine can contribute to better heart health over time.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item4_Screen_3_title">Improve Mental Alertness</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item4_Screen_3_des">Caffeine is known to boost mental alertness and concentration, which can help individuals stay focused and make healthier decisions. This heightened awareness may encourage healthier habits and support a heart-healthy lifestyle, contributing to overall well-being.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item4_Screen_4_title">Note the Drawbacks!</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item4_Screen_4_des">While caffeine has benefits, it can also cause heart palpitations, a temporary increase in blood pressure, and may trigger arrhythmias, especially in individuals with existing heart conditions. \n\nIt’s important to monitor caffeine intake and consult with a healthcare provider if you have concerns.</string>
    <string name="cardio_vascular_health_title_5">Lower Blood Pressure by Drinking Water</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item5_Opening_des">Drinking water is a simple and effective way to help lower high blood pressure. It improves heart function, enhances circulation, and supports kidney function to remove excess sodium, contributing to healthier blood pressure levels.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item5_Screen_1_title">Dehydration and High Blood Pressure</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item5_Screen_1_des">Dehydration can contribute to high blood pressure by reducing blood volume, causing the heart to work harder to pump blood. This increased strain on the heart and blood vessels can result in long-term damage and raise the risk of heart disease</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item5_Screen_2_title">Water Increases Blood Flow</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item5_Screen_2_des">Drinking water helps keep blood vessels hydrated and dilated, improving blood flow and lowering blood pressure. Additionally, water aids in the production of urine, helping to flush excess sodium from the body, which can otherwise contribute to high blood pressure.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item5_Screen_3_title">Water Reduces Oxidative Stress</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item5_Screen_3_des">Drinking water can help reduce oxidative stress, especially in individuals with coronary artery disease. This reduction in oxidative stress promotes better blood vessel function and supports overall cardiovascular health.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item5_Screen_4_title">How Much Water Should You Drink?</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item5_Screen_4_des">Water needs vary based on age, activity, and health. For accurate intake, consider using an app. If you have high blood pressure, consult your doctor to determine the right amount for your needs.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item5_Screen_5_title">Tips for Staying Hydrated</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item5_Screen_5_des">• Carry a water bottle and sip regularly.\n• Drink water before meals and during/after exercise.\n• Eat water-rich foods like watermelon, cucumber, and celery.\n• Avoid sugary and caffeinated drinks like soda and coffee.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item5_Screen_6_title">Know Blood Pressure Ranges</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item5_Screen_6_des">• Normal: 90/60 mmHg to 120/80 mmHg.\n• Low: Below 90/60 mmHg.\n• Hypertensive: Above normal levels.</string>
    <string name="cardio_vascular_health_title_6">Drink Water for a Healthy Heart</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item6_Opening_des">It might surprise you, but simply drinking water can support proper heart function and enhance overall heart health. \n\nHere are some key benefits of staying hydrated for your heart:</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item6_Screen_1_title">Regulate Blood Pressure</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item6_Screen_1_des">Dehydration can lead to a drop in blood pressure, putting strain on the heart. Drinking enough water helps maintain proper blood volume and pressure, which is vital for healthy heart function.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item6_Screen_2_title">Reduce Risk of Heart Disease</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item6_Screen_2_des">Studies show that men who drank five or more glasses of water daily had a 41% lower risk of heart failure and a 54% lower risk of fatal heart disease compared to those who consumed two or fewer glasses per day.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item6_Screen_3_title">Reduce Cholesterol</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item6_Screen_3_des">Drinking more water can help reduce both total cholesterol and LDL (bad) cholesterol levels. \n\nBy flushing out excess cholesterol and toxins through urine, water prevents the buildup of plaque in the arteries, which can lower the risk of cardiovascular diseases.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item6_Screen_4_title">Regulate Heart Rate</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item6_Screen_4_des">Dehydration can cause the heart to work harder, leading to an increased heart rate. Staying hydrated helps ensure the heart maintains a normal rate, reducing unnecessary strain on the heart and promoting overall heart health.</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item6_Screen_5_title">Lower Risk of Kidney Stones</string>
    <string name="Cv_Item6_Screen_5_des">Drinking enough water helps flush out minerals and substances that can form kidney stones, reducing the risk of developing them. \n\nKidney stones can damage both the kidneys and the heart, so proper hydration is essential for maintaining overall health.</string>
    <string name="cardio_vascular_health">Cardiovascular Health</string>

</resources>